<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome</title>
    <link>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Welcome</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2016-19 &lt;a href=&#39;https://github.com/siegerts/hugo-theme-basic&#39;&gt;Hugo Theme Basic&lt;/a&gt;. Made by &lt;a href=&#39;https://twitter.com/siegerts&#39;&gt;@siegerts&lt;/a&gt;.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>niceR code with functional programming</title>
      <link>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/post/nicer-code-with-functional-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/post/nicer-code-with-functional-programming/</guid>
      <description>At the end of this blog post, you will be able to:
Describe functional programming concepts Write functional programming code using purrr package in R If you are anything like me, you probably focused primarily on learning statistics, machine learning and programming on a smaller scale early on in your data science journey. However, as you take on increasingly complex projects, you may find yourself thinking about more and more about structuring your project well and writing code that is easy to understand, debug, reuse, and maintain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getting started with bayesian inference</title>
      <link>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/post/getting-started-with-bayesian-inference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/post/getting-started-with-bayesian-inference/</guid>
      <description>In my previous post, we spoke about hypothesis testing from a frequentist perspective. This is the method that is commonly taught in STAT101 classes. But for many decades, some statisticians have argued for another approach to conduct statistical analysis based on bayes theorem.
As someone who is new to this approach to statistics, my goal in this blogpost is to break down what I’ve learned about the basics of bayesian inference in a way that is (hopefully) easy to follow along if you’re familiar with frequentist methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on edward jenner and creativity</title>
      <link>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/post/on-edward-jenner-and-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/post/on-edward-jenner-and-creativity/</guid>
      <description>One common question that’s on everyone’s minds as we fiercely scrub our hands, pool our resources, conserve our consumption, stock up (but not hoard), invent calculus or write King Lear is: when will this end? Nobody knows what the answer to that question is but we are all in agreement that it could be in the faraway promise land of vaccines.
Although vaccination now is a common method to provide long-term protection against a disease, it was unheard of until about 200 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/project/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 16:53:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/project/hugo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about me</title>
      <link>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apoorvasrinivasanblog.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Apoorva. I&amp;rsquo;m currently building CurieLabs. Previously, I&amp;rsquo;ve built machine learning algorithms for early cancer detection at Intervenn and detecting depression using passive sensor data from smartphones at Columbia University.
I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about ML/AI in biotech and healthcare, making tools for accelerating science and increasing access to education. I&amp;rsquo;m also an avid reader, an unremarkable writer, and a yoga instructor. I live in San Francisco with my cat, Softmax.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
