<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Welcome</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2016-19 &lt;a href=&#39;https://github.com/siegerts/hugo-theme-basic&#39;&gt;Hugo Theme Basic&lt;/a&gt;. Made by &lt;a href=&#39;https://twitter.com/siegerts&#39;&gt;@siegerts&lt;/a&gt;.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>computational psychiatry</title>
      <link>/post/computational-psychiatry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/computational-psychiatry/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>how to get a data science job during a pandemic with no experience</title>
      <link>/post/how-to-get-a-data-science-job-during-a-pandemic-with-no-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-to-get-a-data-science-job-during-a-pandemic-with-no-experience/</guid>
      <description>test commit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getting started with bayesian inference</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started-with-bayesian-inference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started-with-bayesian-inference/</guid>
      <description>In my previous post, we spoke about hypothesis testing from a frequentist perspective. This is the method that is commonly taught in STAT101 classes. But for many decades, some statisticians have argued for another approach to conduct statistical analysis based on bayes theorem.
As someone who is new to this approach to statistics, my goal in this blogpost is to break down what I’ve learned about the basics of bayesian inference in a way that is (hopefully) easy to follow along if you’re familiar with frequentist methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>introduction to hypothesis testing</title>
      <link>/post/hypothesis-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hypothesis-testing/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to my brand new website! I’ve started this blog to think through various statistical concepts and techniques and hopefully they’ll be useful to you too. Let’s start with every statisticians favorite flex: hypothesis testing
There’s two main branches of statistics. One, where we analyze and summarize the data we have. Other where we infer stuff about a population based on some sample data we collect. This is called inferential statistics and hypothesis testing is an important part of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on edward jenner and creativity</title>
      <link>/post/on-edward-jenner-and-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/on-edward-jenner-and-creativity/</guid>
      <description>One common question that’s on everyone’s minds as we fiercely scrub our hands, pool our resources, conserve our consumption, stock up (but not hoard), invent calculus or write King Lear is: when will this end? Nobody knows what the answer to that question is but we are all in agreement that it could be in the faraway promise land of vaccines.
Although vaccination now is a common method to provide long-term protection against a disease, it was unheard of until about 200 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>